{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353617590","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353617590"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 8d9b0559-085b-4ae6-bfef-958b39b513c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" njaa_njaa-hadithi-hapa-shule"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" njaa"," userResponse":" njaa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353640843","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353640843"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 8d9b0559-085b-4ae6-bfef-958b39b513c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" yake_tena-kuwa-kisha-yake"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" yake"," userResponse":" yake"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353675964","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353675964"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 8d9b0559-085b-4ae6-bfef-958b39b513c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kichekesho_madirisha-kabati-kichekesho-pumua"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" kichekesho"," userResponse":" kichekesho"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353702295","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353702295"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 8d9b0559-085b-4ae6-bfef-958b39b513c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kimya_kuliko-tamu-ndiyo-kimya"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" kimya"," userResponse":" kimya"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353720820","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353720820"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 8d9b0559-085b-4ae6-bfef-958b39b513c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nini_mamba-nini-moto-katika"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" nini"," userResponse":" katika"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353723505","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353723505"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 8d9b0559-085b-4ae6-bfef-958b39b513c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nini_mamba-nini-moto-katika"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" nini"," userResponse":" moto"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353726191","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353726191"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 8d9b0559-085b-4ae6-bfef-958b39b513c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nini_mamba-nini-moto-katika"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" nini"," userResponse":" nini"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353735167","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353735163"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 8d9b0559-085b-4ae6-bfef-958b39b513c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" nini_mamba-nini-moto-katika"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353735304","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353735304"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 8d9b0559-085b-4ae6-bfef-958b39b513c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anaona ____________."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ____________"," userResponse":" HAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353745330","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353745330"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 8d9b0559-085b-4ae6-bfef-958b39b513c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Nadhani anaona ____________."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353751468","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353751468"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 8d9b0559-085b-4ae6-bfef-958b39b513c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Nadhani anaona ____________."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.uc:A..Z.vow.5.asc.say.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353759386","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353759386"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 8d9b0559-085b-4ae6-bfef-958b39b513c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Nadhani anaona ____________."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353826360","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353826359"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" acc5276e-9707-41e2-9458-c5014ff33cde"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tena_tena-zake-za-fisi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" tena"," userResponse":" tena"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353845742","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353845739"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" acc5276e-9707-41e2-9458-c5014ff33cde"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" tena_tena-zake-za-fisi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353845878","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353845878"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" acc5276e-9707-41e2-9458-c5014ff33cde"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hamisi alifurahi ____________."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ____________"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353856523","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353856523"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 851accdd-5915-4abb-a56e-323d148142af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" asali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASALI"," userResponse":" ASALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353860211","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353860211"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 851accdd-5915-4abb-a56e-323d148142af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" asali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASALI"," userResponse":" ASALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353861815","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353861815"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 851accdd-5915-4abb-a56e-323d148142af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anaoga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAOGA"," userResponse":" ANAOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353864607","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353864606"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 851accdd-5915-4abb-a56e-323d148142af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anaoga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAOGA"," userResponse":" ANAOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353866168","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353866168"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 851accdd-5915-4abb-a56e-323d148142af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353873729","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353873729"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 851accdd-5915-4abb-a56e-323d148142af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353875345","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353875344"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 851accdd-5915-4abb-a56e-323d148142af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAKULA"," userResponse":" ANAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353883229","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353883229"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 851accdd-5915-4abb-a56e-323d148142af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAKULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353884786","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353884786"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 851accdd-5915-4abb-a56e-323d148142af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" alicheza"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHEZA"," userResponse":" ALICHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353887631","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353887631"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 851accdd-5915-4abb-a56e-323d148142af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" alicheza"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHEZA"," userResponse":" ALICHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353889239","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353889239"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 851accdd-5915-4abb-a56e-323d148142af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" andika"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANDIKA"," userResponse":" ANDIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353891745","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353891745"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 851accdd-5915-4abb-a56e-323d148142af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" andika"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANDIKA"," userResponse":" ANDIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353893343","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353893343"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 851accdd-5915-4abb-a56e-323d148142af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anasoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANASOMA"," userResponse":" ANASOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353896046","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353896046"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 851accdd-5915-4abb-a56e-323d148142af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anasoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANASOMA"," userResponse":" ANASOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353897616","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353897615"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 851accdd-5915-4abb-a56e-323d148142af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" akalala"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKALALA"," userResponse":" AKALALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353902580","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353902579"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 851accdd-5915-4abb-a56e-323d148142af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" akalala"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKALALA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353904169","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353904169"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 851accdd-5915-4abb-a56e-323d148142af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" andazi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANDAZI"," userResponse":" ANDAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353907969","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353907969"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 851accdd-5915-4abb-a56e-323d148142af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" andazi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANDAZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353909603","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353909603"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 851accdd-5915-4abb-a56e-323d148142af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anacheza"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANACHEZA"," userResponse":" ANACHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353914294","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353914294"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 851accdd-5915-4abb-a56e-323d148142af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anacheza"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANACHEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353915874","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353915874"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 851accdd-5915-4abb-a56e-323d148142af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anguka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGUKA"," userResponse":" ANGUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353921587","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353921587"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 851accdd-5915-4abb-a56e-323d148142af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anguka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGUKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353923614","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353923613"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 851accdd-5915-4abb-a56e-323d148142af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" anguka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353923856","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353923856"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 851accdd-5915-4abb-a56e-323d148142af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anguka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGUKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353936853","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353936853"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 7ba0533b-d8d7-415a-8777-a58fda09fbe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" asali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASALI"," userResponse":" ASALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353937480","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353937479"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 7ba0533b-d8d7-415a-8777-a58fda09fbe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" asali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353937594","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353937594"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 7ba0533b-d8d7-415a-8777-a58fda09fbe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" asali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASALI"," userResponse":" ASALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353946157","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353946157"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 7ba0533b-d8d7-415a-8777-a58fda09fbe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" asali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353957818","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353957817"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4b80980c-5fbd-4274-934b-75855b0f634b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" asali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASALI"," userResponse":" ASALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353963330","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353963330"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4b80980c-5fbd-4274-934b-75855b0f634b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" asali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353964910","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353964910"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4b80980c-5fbd-4274-934b-75855b0f634b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anaoga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAOGA"," userResponse":" ANAOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353971912","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353971912"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4b80980c-5fbd-4274-934b-75855b0f634b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anaoga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAOGA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353973504","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353973504"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4b80980c-5fbd-4274-934b-75855b0f634b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353981217","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353981216"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4b80980c-5fbd-4274-934b-75855b0f634b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353982814","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353982813"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4b80980c-5fbd-4274-934b-75855b0f634b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAKULA"," userResponse":" ANAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353984521","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353984521"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4b80980c-5fbd-4274-934b-75855b0f634b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAKULA"," userResponse":" ANAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353985558","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353985557"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4b80980c-5fbd-4274-934b-75855b0f634b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" andika"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANDIKA"," userResponse":" ANAKULA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353986109","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353986109"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4b80980c-5fbd-4274-934b-75855b0f634b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" andika"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANDIKA"," userResponse":" ANDIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353995825","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353995825"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4b80980c-5fbd-4274-934b-75855b0f634b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" andika"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353995967","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353995966"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4b80980c-5fbd-4274-934b-75855b0f634b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" andika"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANDIKA"," userResponse":" ANDIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354005900","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354005900"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354006513","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354006513"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354007286","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354007286"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHETU"," userResponse":" CHETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354008440","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354008440"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANAISHI"," userResponse":" PANAISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354008885","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354008885"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354009658","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354009658"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIIO"," userResponse":" KIIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354012073","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354012071"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354012908","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354012907"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIIO"," userResponse":" KIIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354013746","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354013746"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" ANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354014394","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354014392"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAKA"," userResponse":" PAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354014624","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354014622"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354015353","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354015353"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MADOA"," userResponse":" MADOA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354016205","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354016205"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MEUSI"," userResponse":" MEUSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354016404","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354016404"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354017244","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354017244"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MEUPE"," userResponse":" MEUPE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354017847","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354017847"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354018400","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354018400"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINA"," userResponse":" JINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354019227","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354019227"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFI"," userResponse":" SAFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354021937","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354021937"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio anapoenda kazini anaacha mlango wazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354022694","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354022693"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio anapoenda kazini anaacha mlango wazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIIO"," userResponse":" KIIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354023740","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354023740"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio anapoenda kazini anaacha mlango wazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAPOENDA"," userResponse":" ANAPOENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354024689","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354024688"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio anapoenda kazini anaacha mlango wazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZINI"," userResponse":" KAZINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354025885","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354025885"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio anapoenda kazini anaacha mlango wazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAACHA"," userResponse":" ANAACHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354026489","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354026489"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio anapoenda kazini anaacha mlango wazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLANGO"," userResponse":" MLANGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354027245","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354027245"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio anapoenda kazini anaacha mlango wazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZI"," userResponse":" WAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354030433","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354030433"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi anakaa katikati ya mlango na kuilinda nyumba ya Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFI"," userResponse":" SAFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354031380","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354031380"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi anakaa katikati ya mlango na kuilinda nyumba ya Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAKAA"," userResponse":" ANAKAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354032477","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354032477"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi anakaa katikati ya mlango na kuilinda nyumba ya Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" KATIKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354032560","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354032560"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi anakaa katikati ya mlango na kuilinda nyumba ya Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354033429","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354033429"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi anakaa katikati ya mlango na kuilinda nyumba ya Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLANGO"," userResponse":" MLANGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354034031","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354034030"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi anakaa katikati ya mlango na kuilinda nyumba ya Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354034896","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354034896"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi anakaa katikati ya mlango na kuilinda nyumba ya Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUILINDA"," userResponse":" KUILINDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354035443","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354035443"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi anakaa katikati ya mlango na kuilinda nyumba ya Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354035652","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354035652"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi anakaa katikati ya mlango na kuilinda nyumba ya Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354036129","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354036128"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi anakaa katikati ya mlango na kuilinda nyumba ya Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354036922","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354036922"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi anakaa katikati ya mlango na kuilinda nyumba ya Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIIO"," userResponse":" KIIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354039924","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354039922"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa wa jirani akikaribia Safi anamkodolea macho na kumunyooshea kucha zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBWA"," userResponse":" MBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354040111","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354040111"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa wa jirani akikaribia Safi anamkodolea macho na kumunyooshea kucha zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354040910","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354040910"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa wa jirani akikaribia Safi anamkodolea macho na kumunyooshea kucha zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIRANI"," userResponse":" JIRANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354042340","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354042340"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa wa jirani akikaribia Safi anamkodolea macho na kumunyooshea kucha zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIKARIBIA"," userResponse":" AKIKARIBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354043318","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354043318"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa wa jirani akikaribia Safi anamkodolea macho na kumunyooshea kucha zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFI"," userResponse":" SAFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354045160","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354045160"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa wa jirani akikaribia Safi anamkodolea macho na kumunyooshea kucha zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAMKODOLEA"," userResponse":" ANAMKODOLEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354045868","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354045868"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa wa jirani akikaribia Safi anamkodolea macho na kumunyooshea kucha zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHO"," userResponse":" MACHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354046411","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354046411"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa wa jirani akikaribia Safi anamkodolea macho na kumunyooshea kucha zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354047831","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354047831"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa wa jirani akikaribia Safi anamkodolea macho na kumunyooshea kucha zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMUNYOOSHEA"," userResponse":" KUMUNYOOSHEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354048570","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354048570"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa wa jirani akikaribia Safi anamkodolea macho na kumunyooshea kucha zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHA"," userResponse":" KUCHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354049360","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354049359"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa wa jirani akikaribia Safi anamkodolea macho na kumunyooshea kucha zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354052199","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354052198"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa anatoroka na kurudi kwao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBWA"," userResponse":" MBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354053717","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354053717"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa anatoroka na kurudi kwao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANATOROKA"," userResponse":" ANATOROKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354054005","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354054005"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa anatoroka na kurudi kwao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354054665","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354054665"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa anatoroka na kurudi kwao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUDI"," userResponse":" KURUDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354055114","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354055114"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa anatoroka na kurudi kwao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAO"," userResponse":" KWAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354058610","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354058609"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani akitokezea Safi yu tayari kumkwaruza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIRANI"," userResponse":" JIRANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354060222","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354060222"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani akitokezea Safi yu tayari kumkwaruza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKITOKEZEA"," userResponse":" AKITOKEZEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354061575","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354061575"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani akitokezea Safi yu tayari kumkwaruza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFI"," userResponse":" SAFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354061834","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354061833"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani akitokezea Safi yu tayari kumkwaruza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YU"," userResponse":" YU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354062828","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354062828"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani akitokezea Safi yu tayari kumkwaruza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAYARI"," userResponse":" TAYARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354064300","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354064299"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani akitokezea Safi yu tayari kumkwaruza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMKWARUZA"," userResponse":" KUMKWARUZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354067641","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354067641"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani anageuka mbio na kwenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIRANI"," userResponse":" JIRANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354068815","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354068815"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani anageuka mbio na kwenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAGEUKA"," userResponse":" ANAGEUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354069565","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354069565"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani anageuka mbio na kwenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBIO"," userResponse":" MBIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354070196","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354070196"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani anageuka mbio na kwenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354070756","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354070756"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani anageuka mbio na kwenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354071300","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354071299"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani anageuka mbio na kwenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354074430","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354074430"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akihisi njaa anafunga mlango kwa kuusukuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFI"," userResponse":" SAFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354075346","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354075345"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akihisi njaa anafunga mlango kwa kuusukuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIHISI"," userResponse":" AKIHISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354076087","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354076086"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akihisi njaa anafunga mlango kwa kuusukuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354077408","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354077408"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akihisi njaa anafunga mlango kwa kuusukuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAFUNGA"," userResponse":" ANAFUNGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354078167","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354078167"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akihisi njaa anafunga mlango kwa kuusukuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLANGO"," userResponse":" MLANGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354078414","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354078414"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akihisi njaa anafunga mlango kwa kuusukuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354079900","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354079899"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akihisi njaa anafunga mlango kwa kuusukuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUUSUKUMA"," userResponse":" KUUSUKUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354083586","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354083586"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaingia ndani na kula chakula chake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAINGIA"," userResponse":" ANAINGIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354084214","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354084214"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaingia ndani na kula chakula chake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354084441","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354084441"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaingia ndani na kula chakula chake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354085027","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354085027"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaingia ndani na kula chakula chake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULA"," userResponse":" KULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354085800","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354085800"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaingia ndani na kula chakula chake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354086551","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354086551"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaingia ndani na kula chakula chake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKE"," userResponse":" CHAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354089920","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354089919"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akimaliza anaruka juu ya sofa na kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFI"," userResponse":" SAFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354091503","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354091502"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akimaliza anaruka juu ya sofa na kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIMALIZA"," userResponse":" AKIMALIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354092890","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354092889"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akimaliza anaruka juu ya sofa na kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANARUKA"," userResponse":" ANARUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354093602","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354093601"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akimaliza anaruka juu ya sofa na kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354093839","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354093839"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akimaliza anaruka juu ya sofa na kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354094439","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354094439"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akimaliza anaruka juu ya sofa na kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SOFA"," userResponse":" SOFA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354094659","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354094658"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akimaliza anaruka juu ya sofa na kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354095501","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354095501"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akimaliza anaruka juu ya sofa na kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULALA"," userResponse":" KULALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354098837","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354098837"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unachosikia ni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNACHOSIKIA"," userResponse":" UNACHOSIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354099215","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354099215"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unachosikia ni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354100170","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354100170"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unachosikia ni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PURR"," userResponse":" PURR"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354103212","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354103211"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio akiwasili Safi hujinyoosha kwa furaha na kumkaribisha nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354104170","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354104170"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio akiwasili Safi hujinyoosha kwa furaha na kumkaribisha nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIIO"," userResponse":" KIIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354105686","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354105685"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio akiwasili Safi hujinyoosha kwa furaha na kumkaribisha nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIWASILI"," userResponse":" AKIWASILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354106696","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354106696"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio akiwasili Safi hujinyoosha kwa furaha na kumkaribisha nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFI"," userResponse":" SAFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354108128","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354108128"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio akiwasili Safi hujinyoosha kwa furaha na kumkaribisha nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUJINYOOSHA"," userResponse":" HUJINYOOSHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354109963","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354109963"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio akiwasili Safi hujinyoosha kwa furaha na kumkaribisha nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354111143","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354111143"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio akiwasili Safi hujinyoosha kwa furaha na kumkaribisha nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FURAHA"," userResponse":" FURAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354111425","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354111425"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio akiwasili Safi hujinyoosha kwa furaha na kumkaribisha nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354112732","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354112731"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio akiwasili Safi hujinyoosha kwa furaha na kumkaribisha nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMKARIBISHA"," userResponse":" KUMKARIBISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354113788","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354113788"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio akiwasili Safi hujinyoosha kwa furaha na kumkaribisha nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354116746","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354116746"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio na Safi wanaketi karibu na moto kila mmoja akisoma gazeti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354117413","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354117413"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio na Safi wanaketi karibu na moto kila mmoja akisoma gazeti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIIO"," userResponse":" KIIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354117618","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354117617"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio na Safi wanaketi karibu na moto kila mmoja akisoma gazeti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354118235","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354118235"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio na Safi wanaketi karibu na moto kila mmoja akisoma gazeti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFI"," userResponse":" SAFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354119409","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354119409"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio na Safi wanaketi karibu na moto kila mmoja akisoma gazeti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAKETI"," userResponse":" WANAKETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354120093","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354120093"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio na Safi wanaketi karibu na moto kila mmoja akisoma gazeti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" KARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354120368","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354120368"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio na Safi wanaketi karibu na moto kila mmoja akisoma gazeti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354121281","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354121281"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio na Safi wanaketi karibu na moto kila mmoja akisoma gazeti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354122378","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354122378"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio na Safi wanaketi karibu na moto kila mmoja akisoma gazeti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354123241","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354123241"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio na Safi wanaketi karibu na moto kila mmoja akisoma gazeti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354124446","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354124446"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio na Safi wanaketi karibu na moto kila mmoja akisoma gazeti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKISOMA"," userResponse":" AKISOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354125721","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354125721"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio na Safi wanaketi karibu na moto kila mmoja akisoma gazeti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GAZETI"," userResponse":" GAZETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354128296","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354128295"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio na Safi wanaketi karibu na moto kila mmoja akisoma gazeti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354128422","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354128422"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 858c0e6d-4edd-4b70-9333-d4deeaa071f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio na Safi wanaketi karibu na moto kila mmoja akisoma gazeti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GAZETI"," userResponse":" GAZETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354142784","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354142784"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 25759ca4-dcd6-4a11-aab3-58d2b3811280"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354143417","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354143416"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 25759ca4-dcd6-4a11-aab3-58d2b3811280"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354143849","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354143849"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 25759ca4-dcd6-4a11-aab3-58d2b3811280"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354143935","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354143935"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 25759ca4-dcd6-4a11-aab3-58d2b3811280"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354153298","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354153297"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" ae0d11e7-95aa-4707-87c1-2d744bf455a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo a a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354154042","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354154041"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" ae0d11e7-95aa-4707-87c1-2d744bf455a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo a a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIYO"," userResponse":" NDIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354154869","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354154869"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" ae0d11e7-95aa-4707-87c1-2d744bf455a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo a a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354155752","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354155751"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" ae0d11e7-95aa-4707-87c1-2d744bf455a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo a a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354156339","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354156339"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" ae0d11e7-95aa-4707-87c1-2d744bf455a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo a a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354157089","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354157089"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" ae0d11e7-95aa-4707-87c1-2d744bf455a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo a a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354159588","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354159588"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" ae0d11e7-95aa-4707-87c1-2d744bf455a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama embe a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKO"," userResponse":" IKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354160105","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354160105"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" ae0d11e7-95aa-4707-87c1-2d744bf455a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama embe a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354160952","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354160952"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" ae0d11e7-95aa-4707-87c1-2d744bf455a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama embe a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354161912","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354161912"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" ae0d11e7-95aa-4707-87c1-2d744bf455a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama embe a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354162463","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354162463"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" ae0d11e7-95aa-4707-87c1-2d744bf455a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama embe a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354163176","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354163176"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" ae0d11e7-95aa-4707-87c1-2d744bf455a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama embe a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354166068","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354166067"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" ae0d11e7-95aa-4707-87c1-2d744bf455a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo e e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354166788","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354166787"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" ae0d11e7-95aa-4707-87c1-2d744bf455a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo e e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIYO"," userResponse":" NDIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354166902","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354166901"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" ae0d11e7-95aa-4707-87c1-2d744bf455a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo e e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354168324","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354168323"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" ae0d11e7-95aa-4707-87c1-2d744bf455a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo e e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354168713","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354168712"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" ae0d11e7-95aa-4707-87c1-2d744bf455a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo e e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354168758","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354168758"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" ae0d11e7-95aa-4707-87c1-2d744bf455a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo e e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354172416","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354172416"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" ae0d11e7-95aa-4707-87c1-2d744bf455a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina mkia chini e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INA"," userResponse":" INA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354173075","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354173075"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" ae0d11e7-95aa-4707-87c1-2d744bf455a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina mkia chini e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKIA"," userResponse":" MKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354174009","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354174008"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" ae0d11e7-95aa-4707-87c1-2d744bf455a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina mkia chini e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354174885","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354174885"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" ae0d11e7-95aa-4707-87c1-2d744bf455a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina mkia chini e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354175106","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354175106"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" ae0d11e7-95aa-4707-87c1-2d744bf455a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina mkia chini e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354175145","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354175144"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" ae0d11e7-95aa-4707-87c1-2d744bf455a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina mkia chini e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354179395","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354179395"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" ae0d11e7-95aa-4707-87c1-2d744bf455a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo i i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354180011","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354180011"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" ae0d11e7-95aa-4707-87c1-2d744bf455a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo i i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIYO"," userResponse":" NDIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354180095","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354180095"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" ae0d11e7-95aa-4707-87c1-2d744bf455a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo i i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354180884","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354180884"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" ae0d11e7-95aa-4707-87c1-2d744bf455a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo i i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354181802","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354181802"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" ae0d11e7-95aa-4707-87c1-2d744bf455a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo i i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354183031","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354183030"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" ae0d11e7-95aa-4707-87c1-2d744bf455a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo i i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354185233","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354185233"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" ae0d11e7-95aa-4707-87c1-2d744bf455a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina kofia juu i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INA"," userResponse":" INA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354185926","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354185925"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" ae0d11e7-95aa-4707-87c1-2d744bf455a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina kofia juu i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOFIA"," userResponse":" KOFIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354186194","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354186194"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" ae0d11e7-95aa-4707-87c1-2d744bf455a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina kofia juu i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354187266","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354187266"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" ae0d11e7-95aa-4707-87c1-2d744bf455a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina kofia juu i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354187818","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354187818"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" ae0d11e7-95aa-4707-87c1-2d744bf455a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina kofia juu i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354187870","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354187870"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" ae0d11e7-95aa-4707-87c1-2d744bf455a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina kofia juu i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354192309","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354192309"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" ae0d11e7-95aa-4707-87c1-2d744bf455a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo o o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354192912","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354192912"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" ae0d11e7-95aa-4707-87c1-2d744bf455a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo o o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIYO"," userResponse":" NDIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354193730","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354193730"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" ae0d11e7-95aa-4707-87c1-2d744bf455a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo o o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354193866","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354193866"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" ae0d11e7-95aa-4707-87c1-2d744bf455a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo o o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354194617","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354194617"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" ae0d11e7-95aa-4707-87c1-2d744bf455a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo o o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354195946","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354195946"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" ae0d11e7-95aa-4707-87c1-2d744bf455a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo o o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354198388","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354198388"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" ae0d11e7-95aa-4707-87c1-2d744bf455a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama mpira o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKO"," userResponse":" IKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354198892","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354198892"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" ae0d11e7-95aa-4707-87c1-2d744bf455a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama mpira o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354199901","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354199901"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" ae0d11e7-95aa-4707-87c1-2d744bf455a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama mpira o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPIRA"," userResponse":" MPIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354200785","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354200785"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" ae0d11e7-95aa-4707-87c1-2d744bf455a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama mpira o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354201407","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354201407"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" ae0d11e7-95aa-4707-87c1-2d744bf455a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama mpira o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354202205","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354202204"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" ae0d11e7-95aa-4707-87c1-2d744bf455a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama mpira o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354205202","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354205201"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" ae0d11e7-95aa-4707-87c1-2d744bf455a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo u u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354207191","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354207190"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" ae0d11e7-95aa-4707-87c1-2d744bf455a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo u u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIYO"," userResponse":" NDIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354207434","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354207434"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" ae0d11e7-95aa-4707-87c1-2d744bf455a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo u u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354207827","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354207827"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" ae0d11e7-95aa-4707-87c1-2d744bf455a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo u u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354208030","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354208030"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" ae0d11e7-95aa-4707-87c1-2d744bf455a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo u u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354208921","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354208921"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" ae0d11e7-95aa-4707-87c1-2d744bf455a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo u u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354211711","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354211711"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" ae0d11e7-95aa-4707-87c1-2d744bf455a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama kikombe u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKO"," userResponse":" IKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354212181","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354212180"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" ae0d11e7-95aa-4707-87c1-2d744bf455a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama kikombe u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354213183","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354213183"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" ae0d11e7-95aa-4707-87c1-2d744bf455a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama kikombe u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKOMBE"," userResponse":" KIKOMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354213398","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354213397"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" ae0d11e7-95aa-4707-87c1-2d744bf455a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama kikombe u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354214663","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354214660"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" ae0d11e7-95aa-4707-87c1-2d744bf455a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama kikombe u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354215490","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354215490"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" ae0d11e7-95aa-4707-87c1-2d744bf455a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama kikombe u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354218043","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354218042"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" ae0d11e7-95aa-4707-87c1-2d744bf455a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Iko kama kikombe u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354218151","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354218151"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" ae0d11e7-95aa-4707-87c1-2d744bf455a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama kikombe u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354225673","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354225673"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" ae0d11e7-95aa-4707-87c1-2d744bf455a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Iko kama kikombe u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354232258","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354232258"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" ae0d11e7-95aa-4707-87c1-2d744bf455a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Iko kama kikombe u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354241708","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354241708"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna njia nyingi za kusafiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNA"," userResponse":" KUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354242081","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354242081"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna njia nyingi za kusafiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIA"," userResponse":" NJIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354242723","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354242723"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna njia nyingi za kusafiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGI"," userResponse":" NYINGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354242916","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354242915"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna njia nyingi za kusafiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354243808","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354243808"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna njia nyingi za kusafiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAFIRI"," userResponse":" KUSAFIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354246084","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354246084"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nichague gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NICHAGUE"," userResponse":" NICHAGUE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354247137","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354247137"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nichague gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GANI"," userResponse":" GANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354249830","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354249830"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je nitumie ndege?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354250903","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354250903"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je nitumie ndege?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITUMIE"," userResponse":" NITUMIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354251615","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354251615"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je nitumie ndege?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354254417","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354254417"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege inaruka juu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354255395","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354255395"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege inaruka juu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INARUKA"," userResponse":" INARUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354256106","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354256106"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege inaruka juu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354256876","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354256875"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege inaruka juu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354259050","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354259050"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nami naogopa kuruka!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAMI"," userResponse":" NAMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354259822","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354259822"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nami naogopa kuruka!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAOGOPA"," userResponse":" NAOGOPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354260303","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354260303"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nami naogopa kuruka!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" KURUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354265098","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354265096"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au nitumie helikopta?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AU"," userResponse":" AU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354265894","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354265894"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au nitumie helikopta?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITUMIE"," userResponse":" NITUMIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354267022","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354267021"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au nitumie helikopta?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HELIKOPTA"," userResponse":" HELIKOPTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354270000","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354270000"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini helikopta na ndege ni sawa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354270845","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354270844"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini helikopta na ndege ni sawa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HELIKOPTA"," userResponse":" HELIKOPTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354271066","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354271065"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini helikopta na ndege ni sawa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354271435","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354271435"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini helikopta na ndege ni sawa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354271581","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354271581"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini helikopta na ndege ni sawa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354272220","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354272220"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini helikopta na ndege ni sawa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAWA"," userResponse":" SAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354275164","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354275164"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au labda nitatumia gari la moshi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AU"," userResponse":" AU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354276089","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354276089"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au labda nitatumia gari la moshi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LABDA"," userResponse":" LABDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354277001","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354277000"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au labda nitatumia gari la moshi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITATUMIA"," userResponse":" NITATUMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354277634","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354277634"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au labda nitatumia gari la moshi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354277717","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354277717"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au labda nitatumia gari la moshi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354278302","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354278302"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au labda nitatumia gari la moshi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOSHI"," userResponse":" MOSHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354281566","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354281565"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini stesheni iko mbali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354282424","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354282423"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini stesheni iko mbali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" STESHENI"," userResponse":" STESHENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354282865","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354282865"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini stesheni iko mbali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKO"," userResponse":" IKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354283523","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354283523"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini stesheni iko mbali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBALI"," userResponse":" MBALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354284132","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354284132"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini stesheni iko mbali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354286814","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354286814"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitachoka kutembea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITACHOKA"," userResponse":" NITACHOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354287657","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354287656"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitachoka kutembea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTEMBEA"," userResponse":" KUTEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354290591","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354290591"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je nitumie basi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354291785","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354291784"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je nitumie basi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITUMIE"," userResponse":" NITUMIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354292565","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354292565"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je nitumie basi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354295734","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354295734"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji chetu kina basi moja pekee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354296191","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354296191"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji chetu kina basi moja pekee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHETU"," userResponse":" CHETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354296588","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354296588"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji chetu kina basi moja pekee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINA"," userResponse":" KINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354297025","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354297025"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji chetu kina basi moja pekee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354297485","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354297485"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji chetu kina basi moja pekee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354298208","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354298207"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji chetu kina basi moja pekee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEKEE"," userResponse":" PEKEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354301365","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354301364"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda nitatumia lori kusafiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LABDA"," userResponse":" LABDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354302455","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354302454"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda nitatumia lori kusafiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITATUMIA"," userResponse":" NITATUMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354302842","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354302842"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda nitatumia lori kusafiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354303806","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354303805"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda nitatumia lori kusafiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAFIRI"," userResponse":" KUSAFIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354307040","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354307040"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini lori hasa ni la kubebea mizigo mizito."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354307874","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354307874"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini lori hasa ni la kubebea mizigo mizito."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354308822","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354308821"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini lori hasa ni la kubebea mizigo mizito."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HASA"," userResponse":" HASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354309739","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354309738"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini lori hasa ni la kubebea mizigo mizito."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354309843","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354309843"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini lori hasa ni la kubebea mizigo mizito."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354310568","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354310568"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini lori hasa ni la kubebea mizigo mizito."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBEBEA"," userResponse":" KUBEBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354311241","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354311241"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini lori hasa ni la kubebea mizigo mizito."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIZIGO"," userResponse":" MIZIGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354311959","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354311958"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini lori hasa ni la kubebea mizigo mizito."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIZITO"," userResponse":" MIZITO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354314740","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354314739"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je nitumie baiskeli kusafiri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354316092","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354316092"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je nitumie baiskeli kusafiri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITUMIE"," userResponse":" NITUMIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354316902","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354316902"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je nitumie baiskeli kusafiri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAISKELI"," userResponse":" BAISKELI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354318116","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354318116"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je nitumie baiskeli kusafiri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAFIRI"," userResponse":" KUSAFIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354321271","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354321270"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sijui ikiwa baba atanipatia baiskeli yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIJUI"," userResponse":" SIJUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354321812","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354321812"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sijui ikiwa baba atanipatia baiskeli yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKIWA"," userResponse":" IKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354322125","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354322125"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sijui ikiwa baba atanipatia baiskeli yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354323093","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354323093"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sijui ikiwa baba atanipatia baiskeli yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ATANIPATIA"," userResponse":" ATANIPATIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354323870","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354323870"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sijui ikiwa baba atanipatia baiskeli yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAISKELI"," userResponse":" BAISKELI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354324495","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354324494"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sijui ikiwa baba atanipatia baiskeli yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354327264","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354327263"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au nijaribu kusafiri kwa mashua?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AU"," userResponse":" AU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354327992","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354327992"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au nijaribu kusafiri kwa mashua?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIJARIBU"," userResponse":" NIJARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354328733","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354328733"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au nijaribu kusafiri kwa mashua?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAFIRI"," userResponse":" KUSAFIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354328951","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354328950"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au nijaribu kusafiri kwa mashua?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354329692","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354329692"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au nijaribu kusafiri kwa mashua?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUA"," userResponse":" MASHUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354332762","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354332761"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mimi siamini mashua sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354333130","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354333130"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mimi siamini mashua sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354333876","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354333876"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mimi siamini mashua sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIAMINI"," userResponse":" SIAMINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354334491","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354334491"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mimi siamini mashua sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUA"," userResponse":" MASHUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354335092","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354335091"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mimi siamini mashua sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354337830","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354337830"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Najua nitakachotumia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AAH"," userResponse":" AAH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354340453","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354340453"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Najua nitakachotumia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAJUA"," userResponse":" NAJUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354341950","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354341948"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Najua nitakachotumia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAKACHOTUMIA"," userResponse":" NITAKACHOTUMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354345314","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354345313"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitatumia trekta kusafiri!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITATUMIA"," userResponse":" NITATUMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354346003","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354346002"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitatumia trekta kusafiri!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TREKTA"," userResponse":" TREKTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354347083","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354347083"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitatumia trekta kusafiri!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAFIRI"," userResponse":" KUSAFIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354349889","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354349888"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Nitatumia trekta kusafiri!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354350016","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354350016"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4bef7710-f9ad-4ade-a371-415db45f4df2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitatumia trekta kusafiri!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAFIRI"," userResponse":" KUSAFIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354361351","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354361351"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" d69ca9f8-d125-45f0-86bd-18ae7de67f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo a a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354362085","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354362085"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" d69ca9f8-d125-45f0-86bd-18ae7de67f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo a a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIYO"," userResponse":" NDIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354362908","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354362908"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" d69ca9f8-d125-45f0-86bd-18ae7de67f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo a a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354363782","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354363782"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" d69ca9f8-d125-45f0-86bd-18ae7de67f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo a a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354364365","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354364365"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" d69ca9f8-d125-45f0-86bd-18ae7de67f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo a a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354365109","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354365109"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" d69ca9f8-d125-45f0-86bd-18ae7de67f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo a a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354367593","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354367593"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" d69ca9f8-d125-45f0-86bd-18ae7de67f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama embe a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKO"," userResponse":" IKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354368108","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354368108"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" d69ca9f8-d125-45f0-86bd-18ae7de67f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama embe a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354368953","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354368952"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" d69ca9f8-d125-45f0-86bd-18ae7de67f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama embe a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354369906","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354369906"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" d69ca9f8-d125-45f0-86bd-18ae7de67f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama embe a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354370450","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354370450"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" d69ca9f8-d125-45f0-86bd-18ae7de67f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama embe a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354371153","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354371153"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" d69ca9f8-d125-45f0-86bd-18ae7de67f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama embe a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354374023","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354374023"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" d69ca9f8-d125-45f0-86bd-18ae7de67f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo e e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354374744","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354374743"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" d69ca9f8-d125-45f0-86bd-18ae7de67f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo e e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIYO"," userResponse":" NDIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354374857","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354374857"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" d69ca9f8-d125-45f0-86bd-18ae7de67f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo e e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354376270","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354376270"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" d69ca9f8-d125-45f0-86bd-18ae7de67f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo e e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354376659","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354376659"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" d69ca9f8-d125-45f0-86bd-18ae7de67f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo e e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354376694","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354376693"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" d69ca9f8-d125-45f0-86bd-18ae7de67f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo e e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354380405","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354380405"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" d69ca9f8-d125-45f0-86bd-18ae7de67f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina mkia chini e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INA"," userResponse":" INA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354381058","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354381058"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" d69ca9f8-d125-45f0-86bd-18ae7de67f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina mkia chini e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKIA"," userResponse":" MKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354381979","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354381979"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" d69ca9f8-d125-45f0-86bd-18ae7de67f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina mkia chini e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354382856","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354382855"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" d69ca9f8-d125-45f0-86bd-18ae7de67f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina mkia chini e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354383073","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354383073"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" d69ca9f8-d125-45f0-86bd-18ae7de67f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina mkia chini e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354383112","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354383112"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" d69ca9f8-d125-45f0-86bd-18ae7de67f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina mkia chini e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354387402","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354387402"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" d69ca9f8-d125-45f0-86bd-18ae7de67f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo i i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354388016","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354388016"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" d69ca9f8-d125-45f0-86bd-18ae7de67f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo i i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIYO"," userResponse":" NDIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354388100","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354388100"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" d69ca9f8-d125-45f0-86bd-18ae7de67f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo i i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354388883","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354388883"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" d69ca9f8-d125-45f0-86bd-18ae7de67f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo i i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354389803","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354389803"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" d69ca9f8-d125-45f0-86bd-18ae7de67f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo i i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354391026","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354391026"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" d69ca9f8-d125-45f0-86bd-18ae7de67f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo i i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354393261","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354393260"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" d69ca9f8-d125-45f0-86bd-18ae7de67f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina kofia juu i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INA"," userResponse":" INA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354393957","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354393957"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" d69ca9f8-d125-45f0-86bd-18ae7de67f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina kofia juu i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOFIA"," userResponse":" KOFIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354394226","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354394225"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" d69ca9f8-d125-45f0-86bd-18ae7de67f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina kofia juu i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354395302","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354395302"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" d69ca9f8-d125-45f0-86bd-18ae7de67f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina kofia juu i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354395853","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354395852"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" d69ca9f8-d125-45f0-86bd-18ae7de67f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina kofia juu i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354395897","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354395897"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" d69ca9f8-d125-45f0-86bd-18ae7de67f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina kofia juu i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354400325","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354400325"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" d69ca9f8-d125-45f0-86bd-18ae7de67f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo o o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354400931","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354400930"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" d69ca9f8-d125-45f0-86bd-18ae7de67f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo o o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIYO"," userResponse":" NDIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354401749","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354401749"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" d69ca9f8-d125-45f0-86bd-18ae7de67f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo o o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354401883","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354401883"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" d69ca9f8-d125-45f0-86bd-18ae7de67f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo o o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354402635","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354402635"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" d69ca9f8-d125-45f0-86bd-18ae7de67f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo o o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354403962","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354403961"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" d69ca9f8-d125-45f0-86bd-18ae7de67f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo o o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354406384","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354406384"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" d69ca9f8-d125-45f0-86bd-18ae7de67f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama mpira o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKO"," userResponse":" IKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354406885","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354406884"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" d69ca9f8-d125-45f0-86bd-18ae7de67f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama mpira o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354407893","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354407893"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" d69ca9f8-d125-45f0-86bd-18ae7de67f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama mpira o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPIRA"," userResponse":" MPIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354408760","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354408759"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" d69ca9f8-d125-45f0-86bd-18ae7de67f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama mpira o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354409357","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354409356"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" d69ca9f8-d125-45f0-86bd-18ae7de67f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama mpira o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354410161","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354410161"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" d69ca9f8-d125-45f0-86bd-18ae7de67f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama mpira o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354413370","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354413369"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" d69ca9f8-d125-45f0-86bd-18ae7de67f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo u u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354415340","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354415339"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" d69ca9f8-d125-45f0-86bd-18ae7de67f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo u u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIYO"," userResponse":" NDIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354415603","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354415602"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" d69ca9f8-d125-45f0-86bd-18ae7de67f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo u u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354415993","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354415993"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" d69ca9f8-d125-45f0-86bd-18ae7de67f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo u u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354416209","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354416209"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" d69ca9f8-d125-45f0-86bd-18ae7de67f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo u u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354417092","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354417092"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" d69ca9f8-d125-45f0-86bd-18ae7de67f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo u u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354419902","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354419901"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" d69ca9f8-d125-45f0-86bd-18ae7de67f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama kikombe u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKO"," userResponse":" IKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354420387","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354420387"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" d69ca9f8-d125-45f0-86bd-18ae7de67f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama kikombe u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354421398","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354421398"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" d69ca9f8-d125-45f0-86bd-18ae7de67f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama kikombe u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKOMBE"," userResponse":" KIKOMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354421591","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354421591"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" d69ca9f8-d125-45f0-86bd-18ae7de67f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama kikombe u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354422852","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354422851"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" d69ca9f8-d125-45f0-86bd-18ae7de67f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama kikombe u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354423659","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354423659"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" d69ca9f8-d125-45f0-86bd-18ae7de67f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama kikombe u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354426252","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354426252"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" d69ca9f8-d125-45f0-86bd-18ae7de67f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Iko kama kikombe u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354426368","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354426368"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" d69ca9f8-d125-45f0-86bd-18ae7de67f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama kikombe u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354437955","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354437955"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 90113de3-1a1e-4f4c-b216-c476da5ed776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_9v3"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354442008","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354442008"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 90113de3-1a1e-4f4c-b216-c476da5ed776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v5"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354443615","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354443615"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 90113de3-1a1e-4f4c-b216-c476da5ed776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v5"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354445753","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354445753"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 90113de3-1a1e-4f4c-b216-c476da5ed776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v5"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354446983","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354446983"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 90113de3-1a1e-4f4c-b216-c476da5ed776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ND_8v5"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354456432","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354456431"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 90113de3-1a1e-4f4c-b216-c476da5ed776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ND_8v5"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354464823","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354464823"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 90113de3-1a1e-4f4c-b216-c476da5ed776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ND_8v5"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354472347","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354472347"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 90113de3-1a1e-4f4c-b216-c476da5ed776"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ND_8v5"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354484674","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354484674"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" c09235fc-cf17-467b-8721-5660a6c1eab3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_7v5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354486872","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354486872"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" c09235fc-cf17-467b-8721-5660a6c1eab3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_7v5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354490992","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354490991"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" c09235fc-cf17-467b-8721-5660a6c1eab3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v1"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354492684","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354492684"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" c09235fc-cf17-467b-8721-5660a6c1eab3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v1"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354495548","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354495548"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" c09235fc-cf17-467b-8721-5660a6c1eab3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v4"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354501069","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354501069"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" c09235fc-cf17-467b-8721-5660a6c1eab3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ND_6v4"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354514706","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354514706"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 3641d5c7-5f6b-4d18-9ead-b4b4a67e3969"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo a a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354515446","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354515446"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 3641d5c7-5f6b-4d18-9ead-b4b4a67e3969"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo a a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIYO"," userResponse":" NDIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354516276","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354516275"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 3641d5c7-5f6b-4d18-9ead-b4b4a67e3969"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo a a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354517160","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354517160"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 3641d5c7-5f6b-4d18-9ead-b4b4a67e3969"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo a a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354517771","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354517771"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 3641d5c7-5f6b-4d18-9ead-b4b4a67e3969"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo a a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354518515","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354518515"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 3641d5c7-5f6b-4d18-9ead-b4b4a67e3969"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo a a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354521005","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354521005"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 3641d5c7-5f6b-4d18-9ead-b4b4a67e3969"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama embe a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKO"," userResponse":" IKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354521528","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354521528"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 3641d5c7-5f6b-4d18-9ead-b4b4a67e3969"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama embe a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354522389","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354522388"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 3641d5c7-5f6b-4d18-9ead-b4b4a67e3969"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama embe a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354523358","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354523357"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 3641d5c7-5f6b-4d18-9ead-b4b4a67e3969"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama embe a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354523912","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354523912"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 3641d5c7-5f6b-4d18-9ead-b4b4a67e3969"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama embe a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354524625","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354524624"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 3641d5c7-5f6b-4d18-9ead-b4b4a67e3969"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama embe a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354527544","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354527543"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 3641d5c7-5f6b-4d18-9ead-b4b4a67e3969"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo e e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354528263","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354528263"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 3641d5c7-5f6b-4d18-9ead-b4b4a67e3969"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo e e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIYO"," userResponse":" NDIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354528378","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354528378"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 3641d5c7-5f6b-4d18-9ead-b4b4a67e3969"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo e e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354529807","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354529806"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 3641d5c7-5f6b-4d18-9ead-b4b4a67e3969"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo e e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354530204","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354530204"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 3641d5c7-5f6b-4d18-9ead-b4b4a67e3969"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo e e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354530267","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354530267"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 3641d5c7-5f6b-4d18-9ead-b4b4a67e3969"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo e e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354534012","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354534012"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 3641d5c7-5f6b-4d18-9ead-b4b4a67e3969"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina mkia chini e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INA"," userResponse":" INA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354534671","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354534670"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 3641d5c7-5f6b-4d18-9ead-b4b4a67e3969"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina mkia chini e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKIA"," userResponse":" MKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354535592","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354535592"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 3641d5c7-5f6b-4d18-9ead-b4b4a67e3969"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina mkia chini e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354536468","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354536468"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 3641d5c7-5f6b-4d18-9ead-b4b4a67e3969"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina mkia chini e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354536694","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354536694"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 3641d5c7-5f6b-4d18-9ead-b4b4a67e3969"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina mkia chini e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354536727","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354536727"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 3641d5c7-5f6b-4d18-9ead-b4b4a67e3969"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina mkia chini e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354540971","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354540971"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 3641d5c7-5f6b-4d18-9ead-b4b4a67e3969"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo i i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354541593","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354541592"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 3641d5c7-5f6b-4d18-9ead-b4b4a67e3969"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo i i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIYO"," userResponse":" NDIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354541680","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354541680"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 3641d5c7-5f6b-4d18-9ead-b4b4a67e3969"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo i i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354542471","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354542471"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 3641d5c7-5f6b-4d18-9ead-b4b4a67e3969"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo i i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354543398","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354543397"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 3641d5c7-5f6b-4d18-9ead-b4b4a67e3969"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo i i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354544629","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354544629"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 3641d5c7-5f6b-4d18-9ead-b4b4a67e3969"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo i i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354546836","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354546836"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 3641d5c7-5f6b-4d18-9ead-b4b4a67e3969"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina kofia juu i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INA"," userResponse":" INA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354547533","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354547533"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 3641d5c7-5f6b-4d18-9ead-b4b4a67e3969"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina kofia juu i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOFIA"," userResponse":" KOFIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354547807","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354547805"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 3641d5c7-5f6b-4d18-9ead-b4b4a67e3969"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina kofia juu i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354548881","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354548881"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 3641d5c7-5f6b-4d18-9ead-b4b4a67e3969"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina kofia juu i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354549430","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354549430"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 3641d5c7-5f6b-4d18-9ead-b4b4a67e3969"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina kofia juu i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354549487","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354549487"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 3641d5c7-5f6b-4d18-9ead-b4b4a67e3969"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina kofia juu i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354553839","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354553839"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 3641d5c7-5f6b-4d18-9ead-b4b4a67e3969"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo o o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354554443","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354554443"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 3641d5c7-5f6b-4d18-9ead-b4b4a67e3969"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo o o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIYO"," userResponse":" NDIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354555265","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354555265"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 3641d5c7-5f6b-4d18-9ead-b4b4a67e3969"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo o o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354555399","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354555399"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 3641d5c7-5f6b-4d18-9ead-b4b4a67e3969"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo o o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354556159","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354556159"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 3641d5c7-5f6b-4d18-9ead-b4b4a67e3969"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo o o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354557496","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354557496"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 3641d5c7-5f6b-4d18-9ead-b4b4a67e3969"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo o o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354559917","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354559917"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 3641d5c7-5f6b-4d18-9ead-b4b4a67e3969"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama mpira o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKO"," userResponse":" IKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354560416","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354560416"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 3641d5c7-5f6b-4d18-9ead-b4b4a67e3969"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama mpira o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354561432","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354561432"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 3641d5c7-5f6b-4d18-9ead-b4b4a67e3969"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama mpira o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPIRA"," userResponse":" MPIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354562304","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354562303"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 3641d5c7-5f6b-4d18-9ead-b4b4a67e3969"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama mpira o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354562916","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354562916"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 3641d5c7-5f6b-4d18-9ead-b4b4a67e3969"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama mpira o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354563715","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354563715"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 3641d5c7-5f6b-4d18-9ead-b4b4a67e3969"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama mpira o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354565100","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354565099"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 3641d5c7-5f6b-4d18-9ead-b4b4a67e3969"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Iko kama mpira o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354565203","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354565203"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 3641d5c7-5f6b-4d18-9ead-b4b4a67e3969"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama mpira o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354575147","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354575147"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 3641d5c7-5f6b-4d18-9ead-b4b4a67e3969"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Iko kama mpira o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354589851","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354589851"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 3641d5c7-5f6b-4d18-9ead-b4b4a67e3969"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Iko kama mpira o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354601422","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354601422"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" fc9b9494-5913-4db0-aaec-46307ef7bd29"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_0-1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354608777","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354608777"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" fc9b9494-5913-4db0-aaec-46307ef7bd29"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_0-1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354614258","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354614258"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" fc9b9494-5913-4db0-aaec-46307ef7bd29"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_5-4"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354619529","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354619529"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" fc9b9494-5913-4db0-aaec-46307ef7bd29"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_1-0"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354625635","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354625635"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" fc9b9494-5913-4db0-aaec-46307ef7bd29"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_3-2"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354632306","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354632306"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" fc9b9494-5913-4db0-aaec-46307ef7bd29"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_3-2"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354639696","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354639696"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" fc9b9494-5913-4db0-aaec-46307ef7bd29"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_3-2"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354645820","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354645820"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" fc9b9494-5913-4db0-aaec-46307ef7bd29"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_3-2"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354651353","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354651353"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" fc9b9494-5913-4db0-aaec-46307ef7bd29"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_9-8"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354657088","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354657088"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" fc9b9494-5913-4db0-aaec-46307ef7bd29"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_5-4"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354661773","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354661773"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" fc9b9494-5913-4db0-aaec-46307ef7bd29"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_4-3"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354667252","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354667252"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" fc9b9494-5913-4db0-aaec-46307ef7bd29"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_5-4"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354673598","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354673598"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" fc9b9494-5913-4db0-aaec-46307ef7bd29"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_4_5-4"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354689423","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354689423"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" e9efe435-76a7-4aa7-bc50-5ccccc58672e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_o-a-i"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354693618","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354693618"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" e9efe435-76a7-4aa7-bc50-5ccccc58672e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-u-e"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354700851","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354700851"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" e9efe435-76a7-4aa7-bc50-5ccccc58672e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-u-e"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354706528","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354706527"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" e9efe435-76a7-4aa7-bc50-5ccccc58672e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_i-a-o"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354712761","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354712760"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" e9efe435-76a7-4aa7-bc50-5ccccc58672e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_i-a-o"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354717088","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354717088"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" e9efe435-76a7-4aa7-bc50-5ccccc58672e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-i-e"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354720787","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354720787"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" e9efe435-76a7-4aa7-bc50-5ccccc58672e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-e-o"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354724183","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354724182"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" e9efe435-76a7-4aa7-bc50-5ccccc58672e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-i-e"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354727442","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354727442"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" e9efe435-76a7-4aa7-bc50-5ccccc58672e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-e-i"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354730858","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354730858"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" e9efe435-76a7-4aa7-bc50-5ccccc58672e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-i-u"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354734059","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354734059"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" e9efe435-76a7-4aa7-bc50-5ccccc58672e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-o-e"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354737662","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354737662"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" e9efe435-76a7-4aa7-bc50-5ccccc58672e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-e-i"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354743464","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354743464"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" e9efe435-76a7-4aa7-bc50-5ccccc58672e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-e-i"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354852070","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354852070"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" e9efe435-76a7-4aa7-bc50-5ccccc58672e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-e-i"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354852220","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354852219"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 0841b706-5694-4100-8d4e-f206f6b195e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akanunua baiskikeli iliyo refu mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNO"," userResponse":" MNO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354872736","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354872736"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 0841b706-5694-4100-8d4e-f206f6b195e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kisha akanunua baiskikeli iliyo refu mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354872926","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354872926"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 5299a1dd-e434-4c36-8305-1ad013156013"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlango wake ulikuwa chini mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIKUWA"," userResponse":" ULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354887866","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354887866"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 5299a1dd-e434-4c36-8305-1ad013156013"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mlango wake ulikuwa chini mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354897792","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354897791"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 5299a1dd-e434-4c36-8305-1ad013156013"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mlango wake ulikuwa chini mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354912471","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354912471"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4ab1eb90-1a2a-44d7-b4f6-78aa2d726d0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-e-o"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548354919085","data":{"timestamp":" 1548354919085"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4ab1eb90-1a2a-44d7-b4f6-78aa2d726d0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-e-o"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548355020581","data":{"timestamp":" 1548355020581"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4ab1eb90-1a2a-44d7-b4f6-78aa2d726d0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-e-o"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548355024638","data":{"timestamp":" 1548355024638"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4ab1eb90-1a2a-44d7-b4f6-78aa2d726d0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-i-e"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548355028214","data":{"timestamp":" 1548355028214"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4ab1eb90-1a2a-44d7-b4f6-78aa2d726d0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-o-e"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548355031988","data":{"timestamp":" 1548355031988"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4ab1eb90-1a2a-44d7-b4f6-78aa2d726d0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_o-a-i"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548355036344","data":{"timestamp":" 1548355036344"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4ab1eb90-1a2a-44d7-b4f6-78aa2d726d0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-e-i"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548355038488","data":{"timestamp":" 1548355038484"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4ab1eb90-1a2a-44d7-b4f6-78aa2d726d0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-e-i"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548355048005","data":{"timestamp":" 1548355048004"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4ab1eb90-1a2a-44d7-b4f6-78aa2d726d0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-e-i"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548355056378","data":{"timestamp":" 1548355056377"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_211308"," gameId":" 4ab1eb90-1a2a-44d7-b4f6-78aa2d726d0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-e-i"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}